<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ryoAccount.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-31T00:39:13.276Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ryoAccount.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ryoAccount.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Routing in Next.js – How to Set Up Dynamic Routing with Pre-Rendering in Next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-dynamic-routing-in-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-dynamic-routing-in-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T21:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn how to set up dynamic routing in Next.js. You'll also learn about pre-rendering and why it's important. 🔐 Here's what we'll cover:  * You'll get to know getStaticPaths(), one of the core principles of Next.js.  * You'll improve your general Next.js knowledge and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthes Bär</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sort Alphabetically in JavaScript – How to Order by Name in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-alphabetically-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-alphabetically-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T19:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might have an array of words where you want to sort each word alphabetically (from a-z). Or you might have an array of objects containing user information including names, for example, where you want to sort the users by their names. We can do this in JavaScript by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Tech Career in 2022 – A Career Changer's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-a-tech-career/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-a-tech-career/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T16:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing a tech career can be tricky because there are many possible paths to choose from. There's Web Development, Machine Learning, Data Science, DevOps, and many more. But the good news is you don't necessarily have to be a developer to be in the world of tech. This article is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Iroegbu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Shadows? Pure CSS Parallax? Game Back On.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367270</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/scroll-shadows-pure-css-parallax-game-back-on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T14:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris calls scroll shadows one his favorite CSS-Tricks of all time. Lea Verou popularized the pure CSS approach using four layered background gradients with some clever background-attachment magic. The result is a slick scrolling interaction that gives users a hint …
Scroll Shadows? Pure CSS Parallax? Game Back On. originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Authenticate a User with Face Recognition in React.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/authenticate-with-face-recognition-reactjs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/authenticate-with-face-recognition-reactjs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-29T13:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the advent of Web 2.0, authenticating users became a crucial task for developers.  Before Web 2.0, website visitors could only view the content of a web page – there was no interaction. This era of the internet was called Web 1.0. But after Web 2.0, people gained the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrishikesh Pathak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error: failed to push some refs to – How to Fix in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-failed-to-push-some-refs-to-how-to-fix-in-git/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/error-failed-to-push-some-refs-to-how-to-fix-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T20:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When collaborating with other developers using Git, you might encounter the  error: failed to push some refs to [remote repo] error. This error mainly occurs when you attempt to push your local changes to GitHub while the local repository (repo) has not yet been updated with any changes made]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recreating MDN’s Truncated Text Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367170</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/recreating-mdns-truncated-text-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T17:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that MDN rolled out a new design back in March. It’s gorgeous! And there are some sweet CSS-y gems in it that are fun to look at. One of those gems is how card components handle truncated …
Recreating MDN’s Truncated Text Effect originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript replaceAll() – Replace All Instances of a String in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-replaceall-replace-all-instances-of-a-string-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-replaceall-replace-all-instances-of-a-string-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T16:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with a JavaScript program, you might need to replace a character or word with another one. Specifically, you may need to replace not just one but all occurrences of that character or word with something else. There are a few ways you can achieve this with JavaScript. One]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Dictionary Methods – Dictionaries in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-dictionary-methods-dictionaries-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-dictionary-methods-dictionaries-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T15:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, a dictionary is one of the core data structures. It is a sequence of key-value pairs separated by commas and surrounded by curly braces. If you’re familiar with JavaScript, Python dictionaries are like JavaScript objects. Python provides more than 10 methods for working with dictionaries. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Game Development with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-game-development-full-course/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-game-development-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript can be used to develop a bunch of different types of games. And games created with JavaScript can run on almost any device with a web browser. We just published a 10-hour JavaScript game development course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. You will learn to make 2D games with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testable Frontend: The Good, The Bad And The Flaky]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/testable-frontend-architecture/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/testable-frontend-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing is not just about tools and processes. It’s about architecture. In this article, Noam Rosenthal will share his experience on how to organize testing and find the right balance between front-end and subsystems and between different strategies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Noam Rosenthal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript document.ready() – Document Ready JS and jQuery Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-document-ready-jquery-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-document-ready-jquery-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T21:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with JavaScript and the Document Object Model (DOM), you might want your script to run only when the DOM has loaded.  You can do this using the $(document).ready() method in jQuery, or the  DOMContentLoaded event in vanilla JavaScript. In this article, you'll learn how to make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI Chatbot with Redis, Python, and GPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-ai-chatbot-with-redis-python-and-gpt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-ai-chatbot-with-redis-python-and-gpt/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T20:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In order to build a working full-stack application, there are so many moving parts to think about. And you'll need to make many decisions that will be critical to the success of your app. For example, what language will you use and what platform will you deploy on? Are you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Sanwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Unit Testing? How to Perform Unit Tests in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unit-testing-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/unit-testing-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing is an essential part of Software Development. Testing your code ensures that the software you develop works as expected and makes it less vulnerable to attackers. Software testing is a very broad topic. That's why in the software industry, there are separate professionals who specialize in just QA and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Menard Maranan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Redux? Store, Actions, and Reducers Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-redux-store-actions-reducers-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-redux-store-actions-reducers-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T15:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux is a predictable state container for JavaScript apps. So what does that really mean? If we dig deeper into this statement, we see that Redux is a state management library that you can use with any JS library or framework like React, Angular, or Vue. In this article, we'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham De Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[金属でできた鉛筆「メタシル」を使ってA4の紙いっぱいに絵を描いてみたら…強靭すぎて震えた]]></title>
        <id>https://rocketnews24.com/2022/07/27/1661137</id>
        <link href="https://rocketnews24.com/2022/07/27/1661137"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T21:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[どういうことだってばよ……？  最初にそのキャッチコピーを見たとき、頭の中に浮かんだのは大量の「？」マーク。だって、「芯まで金属でできている鉛筆」なんて言われて誰 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Software Architecture Handbook]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-introduction-to-software-architecture-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-introduction-to-software-architecture-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T21:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to talk about a very interesting, vast, and complex topic: software architecture. This is something that used to confuse me quite a bit when I was starting to code. So in this article I'll try to give you a simple, surface-level, easy to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Terraform by Deploying a Jenkins Server on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-terraform-by-deploying-jenkins-server-on-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-terraform-by-deploying-jenkins-server-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T18:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone! Today we're going to learn about Terraform by building a project. Terraform is more than just a tool to boost the productivity of operations teams. You have the chance to transform your developers into operators by implementing Terraform. This can help increase the efficiency of your entire engineering]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test-Driven Development Tutorial – How to Test Your JavaScript and ReactJS Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/test-driven-development-tutorial-how-to-test-javascript-and-reactjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/test-driven-development-tutorial-how-to-test-javascript-and-reactjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T17:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding test-driven development is an essential part of being a prolific software developer. Testing provides a solid platform for building reliable programs. This tutorial will show you all you need to implement test-driven development in your JavaScript and React applications. Table of Contents  1.  What Is Test-Driven Development?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi Sofela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Save and Exit Nano in Terminal – Nano Quit Command]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-save-and-exit-nano-in-terminal-nano-quit-command/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-save-and-exit-nano-in-terminal-nano-quit-command/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T16:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nano is a command line-based code editor known for its simplicity compared to other editors like Vim and Emacs. But if you are new to Nano, performing basic operations like creating files, saving the file, and exiting the editor might be confusing. So, in this article, I want to show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the flat() and flatMap() Methods to Flatten Arrays in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flat-and-flatmap-javascript-array-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flat-and-flatmap-javascript-array-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T16:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'm going to explain how to use the new array methods introduced in ES2019 (EcmaScript 2019) – flat() and flatMap(). You use these methods to flatten arrays. The methods are very useful and easy to use. It will really be cool to use these methods in your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenechukwu Nwobodo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List Sorting – How to Order Lists in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-sorting-how-to-order-lists-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-sorting-how-to-order-lists-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T16:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many reasons you might want to sort lists in your Python applications. In this article, I'll show you how to order lists in ascending and descending order depending on what you need to do. What is a List in Python? A list is a data type in Python]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start Using MongoDB – Database Setup for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-start-using-mongodb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-start-using-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB is an increasingly popular open source NoSQL database. And it has many advantages over traditional SQL databases.  It offers high scalability, reliability, and performance even with a huge amount of data.  This article covers the basics that you need to know to get started with MongoDB and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[object, object] in JavaScript – Meaning in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-object-in-javascript-meaning-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/object-object-in-javascript-meaning-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with objects in JavaScript, you may have come across the [object, object] output. While this may seem irrelevant, it's not necessarily an error.  [object, object] is the string representation of a JavaScript object data type. You'll understand better as we go further in this article. There are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&lt;article&gt; vs. &lt;section&gt;: How To Choose The Right One]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/article-section-elements-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/article-section-elements-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Olushuyi explores a mental model that helps you decide between the `` and `
` elements when writing documents. You will explore how grouping content affects accessibility and how you can make it all count for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Olushuyi Olutimilehin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Key in Object – How to Check if an Object has a Key in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-an-object-has-a-key-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-check-if-an-object-has-a-key-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objects in JavaScript are non-primitive data types that hold an unordered collection of key-value pairs. As you can see in the image above, the key is the property, and each object value must have a key. When interacting with objects, situations might arise that require you to check if a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loading a JSON File in Python – How to Read and Parse JSON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loading-a-json-file-in-python-how-to-read-and-parse-json/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/loading-a-json-file-in-python-how-to-read-and-parse-json/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to read and parse JSON in Python. What is JSON? JSON is short for JavaScript Object Notation. It's a simple syntax for storing data in name-value pairs. Values can be different data types as long as they are valid. Non-acceptable types for JSON include]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python find() – How to Search for a Substring in a String]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-find-how-to-search-for-a-substring-in-a-string/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-find-how-to-search-for-a-substring-in-a-string/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T13:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with a Python program, you might need to search for and locate a specific string inside another string. This is where Python's built-in string methods come in handy. In this article, you will learn how to use Python's built-in find() string method to help you search for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily create a website using Elementor and WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/easily-create-a-website-using-elementor-and-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/easily-create-a-website-using-elementor-and-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elementor makes it simple to create a WordPress website using a drag and drop interface. You don't even need any code! We just published an Elementor course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to easily create your own website. I created this course. I've also made]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Chose Angular to Build a URL Shortener]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367003</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/why-i-chose-angular-to-build-a-url-shortener/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T14:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[URL Shorteners are tools we use to make links shorter than they actually are. With a URL Shortener, you can transform a long link (maybe for a registration form or article) into a shorter version.
Behind the scenes, the long …
Why I Chose Angular to Build a URL Shortener originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming Imposter Syndrome By Developing Your Own Guiding Principles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/overcoming-imposter-syndrome-developing-guiding-principles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/overcoming-imposter-syndrome-developing-guiding-principles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Luis Ouriach helps to develop your own guiding principles to become a better designer so that you can walk into the design critique meetings with more confidence and really deliver the best representation of your ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does // Mean in Python? Operators in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-double-slash-mean-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-double-slash-mean-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, you use the double slash // operator to perform floor division. This  // operator divides the first number by the second number and rounds the result down to the nearest integer (or whole number). In this article, I will show you how to use the // operator]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typeerror: string indices must be integers – How to Fix in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-string-indices-must-be-integers-how-to-fix-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-string-indices-must-be-integers-how-to-fix-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, there are certain iterable objects – lists, tuples, and strings – whose items or characters can be accessed using their index numbers.  For example, to access the first character in a string, you'd do something like this: greet = "Hello World!" print(greet[0]) # H To access the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundup of Recent Document Outline Chatter]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367048</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/roundup-of-recent-document-outline-chatter/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not everyday that HTML headings are the topic de jour, but my folder of saved links is accumulating articles about the recently merged removal of the document outline algorithm in the WHATWG Living Standard.
First off, you should know …
Roundup of Recent Document Outline Chatter originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Apache Cassandra, a NoSQL Database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-apache-a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-apache-a/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Cassandra is a NoSQL database used by some of the largest companies in the world, including Facebook, Netflix, eBay, and Twitter. We just published a full course on Apache Cassandra on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Apache Cassandra is a free and open-source distributed NoSQL database management system designed to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking Back At SmashingConf SF 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/smashingconf-sf-2022-review/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/smashingconf-sf-2022-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that some time has passed since the team returned from SmashingConf San Francisco, we’ve had time to think about the event and wrap up some of the things we all learned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jarijn Nijkamp)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SLIPKNOT、ニュー・アルバム『The End, So Far』リリース決定！新曲「The Dying Song (Time To Sing)」MV公開！]]></title>
        <id>https://gekirock.com/news/2022/07/slipknot_the_end_so_far.php</id>
        <link href="https://gekirock.com/news/2022/07/slipknot_the_end_so_far.php"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SLIPKNOTが、2019年の『We Are Not Your Kind』以来となるニュー・アルバム『The End, So Far』を9月30日にリリースすることが決定した！ 　 同作には、2021年11月にリリースされた「The Chapeltown Rag」など12曲が収録される。 　 また、新曲「The Dying Song (Time To Sing)」のミュージック・ビデオも公開されている！ 　 Slipknot - The Dying Song (Time To Sing) 　 ▼リリース情報 SLIPKNOT ニュー・アルバム 『The End, So Far』 2022.0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center a Div with CSS – 10 Different Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-a-div-with-css-10-different-ways/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-a-div-with-css-10-different-ways/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T22:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a web developer, sometimes centering a div feels like one of the toughest jobs on planet Earth.  Well, not anymore. In this article, you'll learn 10 different ways to center a  div. We will explore how to center divs using the CSS position property, CSS  Flexbox,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham De Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Minimum Viable Product]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-minimum-viable-product/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-minimum-viable-product/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T20:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A minimum viable product (MVP) is a product with just enough features to be usable by early adopters. The goal is to get feedback from these early adopters and learn what features to add or remove from the product before releasing it to a wider audience. In this course, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Think Like a Computer Science Professor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-think-like-a-computer-science-professor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-think-like-a-computer-science-professor/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T19:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many tutorials demonstrate how to build something that the instructor has already fully planned out beforehand. But it can be helpful to see the thought process that goes into building a project completely from scratch. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will demonstrate how an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Objects in JavaScript – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/objects-in-javascript-for-beginners/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/objects-in-javascript-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Declaring multiple variables to hold different values can make your program untidy and cumbersome.  For instance, if you need to store three characteristics each for 10 individuals, having 30 variables individually declared can make your program appear less organized.  So you need a way to group values with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>D.M. Oladele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic Git Commands – How to Use Git in a Real Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-basic-git-and-github-commands/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-basic-git-and-github-commands/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous tutorial [/news/git-and-github-the-basics/] we talked about what version control is, how Git and GitHub work, and how to setup an account with GitHub. Today we will be looking at how to use some basic Git commands in a real project. I created a simple project that we'll be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a "Skip to Main Content" Link to Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-skip-to-main-content-links-to-a-website/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-skip-to-main-content-links-to-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Websites and web applications have increasingly become more complex. But it's still our responsibility, as web developers, to strive for the highest level of accessibility we possibly can.  This isn't always easy, as the range of user accessibility needs can complicate things even further.  Thankfully, various guidelines exist]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Mawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Call a Function in Python – Def Syntax Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-call-a-function-in-python-def-syntax-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-call-a-function-in-python-def-syntax-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python and other programming languages, you can use functions to avoid repeting yourself and to reuse pieces of code. To make functions work, you don’t just write them and say goodbye – you have to call them too. Before you call a function, you need to write it with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logical Properties for Useful Shorthands]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=367064</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/logical-properties-for-useful-shorthands/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Barker with my favorite sorta blog post: short, practical, and leaves you with a valuable nugget for your time. Here, she gets into logical property shorthands in CSS, particularly those that set lengths just on a single axis, …
Logical Properties for Useful Shorthands originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Truffle and Ganache – How to Create and Deploy a Smart Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-truffle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-started-with-truffle/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new technology often means learning a new framework, programming language, IDE, or deployment method. And the blockchain is no different. In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to get started with Truffle [https://trufflesuite.com/docs/vscode-ext/installation-guide/], a Node.js blockchain framework, in Visual Studio Code. How to Install Truffle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagruti Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loop Through an Object in JavaScript – How to Iterate Over an Object in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-iterate-over-objects-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-iterate-over-objects-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript, when you hear the term "loop", you probably think of using the various loop methods like for loops [/news/javascript-for-loops/], forEach() [/news/javascript-foreach-js-array-for-each-example/], map() and others. But in the case of objects, unfortunately, these methods don't work because objects are not iterable. This doesn't mean we can't loop through an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Image Optimization Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/powerful-image-optimization-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/powerful-image-optimization-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing the size of images can have a bigger impact on performance than all other areas combined. In this article, Louis Lazaris covers different tools available for reducing the size of images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert a String to a DateTime Object in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-a-string-to-a-datetime-object-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-convert-a-string-to-a-datetime-object-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T20:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you get dates from raw data, they're typically in the form of string objects. But in this form, you can't access the date's properties like the year, month, and so on.  The solution to this problem is to parse (or convert) the string object into a datetime object]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[colyのTwitter活用事例]]></title>
        <id>https://marketing.twitter.com/ja/success-stories/coly-promise-of-wizard</id>
        <link href="https://marketing.twitter.com/ja/success-stories/coly-promise-of-wizard"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T20:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[スマホゲーム「魔法使いの約束」の周年施策にTwitterを活用した株式会社colyの事例をご紹介します。開始5分でトレンド1位を獲得した”まほやく”の施策とは？今すぐ記事をチェック]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[While Loops in Python – While True Loop Statement Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/while-loops-in-python-while-true-loop-statement-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/while-loops-in-python-while-true-loop-statement-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has many tools and features that can help you automate repetitive tasks. One of those features is loops. Loops are a helpful and frequently used feature in all modern programming languages. Loops are helpful when you want to automate a specific repetitive task or prevent yourself from copying and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Batch Delete Emails in Gmail – Delete Multiple Email Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-batch-delete-emails-in-gmail-delete-multiple-email-messages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-batch-delete-emails-in-gmail-delete-multiple-email-messages/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hear some of my co-workers talk about getting to inbox zero. So I started thinking of a way to clear out my over over 4000 unread messages. And after days of searching around, I found a way. I even went on to delete 20,000 email messages from the trash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Checksum? How to Check if a File was Modified Using the cksum Command in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-last-modified-in-inux-how-to-check-if-two-files-are-same/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/file-last-modified-in-inux-how-to-check-if-two-files-are-same/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are working with files on the command line, you might need to check their modification time and content integrity.  Linux has a powerful command line which allows you to explore multiple aspects of files and filesystems. In case you need to check if file was modified, you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Random Number Generator – How to Generate Numbers with Math.random() and Convert to Integers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-random-number-generator-how-to-generate-with-math-random-and-convert-to-integer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-random-number-generator-how-to-generate-with-math-random-and-convert-to-integer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many applications, you need random numbers. You might need to throw dice in video games, create a private cryptography key, or create a user’s temporary password.  All these applications depend on random number creation. It’s sometimes challenging to differentiate what to use when, and security is a deep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[フロントエンドのトレンドは変化したか？ アンケート結果から分析する2022年のウェブ制作]]></title>
        <id>https://ics.media/entry/220719</id>
        <link href="https://ics.media/entry/220719"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ウェブ業界の当たり前だと思っていることでも、他社の人には違う常識があるかもしれません。自分が業界多数の傾向と違うところはどこなのか・・・、この連載ではアンケートデータから国内のウェブ業界の傾向を分析します。連載8回目となる本記事では「フロントエンドエンジニアの移り変わり」をテーマとしてアンケート結果を紹介します。あなたが最近使っているJAVASCRIPTライブラリ/フレームワークはどれ？（2022年版）国内で最近人気のあるJavaScriptライブラリ/フレームワークはどれでしょうか。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[参考にしたい日本人デザイナー・エンジニアのポートフォリオサイトまとめ]]></title>
        <id>https://arutega.jp/japanese-portfolio</id>
        <link href="https://arutega.jp/japanese-portfolio"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T22:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[就職活動の時期にさしかかっている就活生の皆さんへ贈る、日本人のデザイナー・エンジニアのポートフォリオサイトです。職務経歴をアピールするため、ポートフォリオを作成を検討しているWeb系エンジニアの方向けの記事です。ポートフォリオ作成のポイントやポートフォリオに含めるべき内容と作成時のポイントについてご説明いたします]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Stacked Architecture to Build a Flutter Todo App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-stacked-architecture-todo-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-stacked-architecture-todo-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T22:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter is a UI toolkit for building cross-platform applications. You can build Flutter apps using various state management techniques like the Stacked [https://pub.dev/packages/stacked] architecture.  This article will explain what Stacked architecture is and will guide you through creating a simple Todo App in Flutter with Stacked. Table of Contents]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typeerror: cannot unpack non-iterable nonetype object – How to Fix in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cannot-unpack-non-iterable-nonetype-object-how-to-fix-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-cannot-unpack-non-iterable-nonetype-object-how-to-fix-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with iterable objects like Lists, Sets, and Tuples in Python, you might want to assign the items in these objects to individual variables. This is a process known as unpacking.  During the process of unpacking items in iterable objects, you may get an error that says:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singleton Design Pattern – How it Works in JavaScript with Example Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/singleton-design-pattern-with-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/singleton-design-pattern-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At one point or another, you might need to use global state inside your React apps. This lets you have your data in one place and make sure the required components can access it.  To help you do this, you'll often use some sort of state management library like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keyur Paralkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary Search in Python – How to Code the Algorithm with Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-search-in-python-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/binary-search-in-python-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our daily lives, we're constantly searching for information or trying to find solutions to problems we encounter. When going through search results on the web, we pick the most relevant articles or resources that we think will help us. Search is such a part of our lives because we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tantoluwa Heritage Alabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Puppeteer With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-puppeteer-with-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-puppeteer-with-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Puppeteer is a JavaScript library that allows you to script and interact with browser windows. In this guide, we'll explore the basics of using Puppeteer with Node.js so you can start automating your tests. Prerequisites  * Basic understanding of Node.js  * Basic understanding of Puppeteer  * A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DevTestOps? How to Combine DevOps and TestOps to Build Better Products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-devtestops/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-devtestops/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology is always improving, and developers are always trying to find easier and better ways to improve the software. This is how DevOps came to be, and over time DevTestOps emerged as a new strategy. Today, companies like Spotify apply DevTestOps in software production which makes it easier for them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ezinne Anne Emilia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typeerror: int object is not callable – How to Fix in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-int-object-is-not-callable-how-to-fix-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/typeerror-int-object-is-not-callable-how-to-fix-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, a “Typeerror” occurs when you use different data types in an operation. For example, if you attempt to divide an integer (number) by a string, it leads to a typeerror because an integer data type is not the same as a string. One of those type errors is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Push into an Array in JavaScript – How to Insert an Element into an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-insert-an-element-into-an-array-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-insert-an-element-into-an-array-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The array datatype is one of the most commonly used datatypes when you're working with an ordered list of values. Each value is referred to as an element with a unique id. It stores elements of various datatypes that you can access through a single variable. In practice, an array]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Pattern For The Jamstack: Segmented Rendering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/new-pattern-jamstack-segmented-rendering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/new-pattern-jamstack-segmented-rendering/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Segmented Rendering” is a new pattern and it will change the Jamstack game forever. Let’s try to push the boundaries of static rendering and learn how to apply it to personalized content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Burel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[経産省が「Web3.0政策推進室」設置]]></title>
        <id>https://neweconomy.jp/posts/244611</id>
        <link href="https://neweconomy.jp/posts/244611"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[「Web3.0政策推進室」が経産省大臣官房に設置 経済産業省が、大臣官房に「Web3.0（ウェブ・スリー）政策推進室」を設置したことが7月15日分かった。 発表によると「Web3.0政策推進室」では、海外での事業環境や、国内での事業環境課題について事業者、投資家、法曹、エンジニア等から情報収集を行い、デジタル庁等の関係府省庁と協力してWeb3.0に関連する事業環境整備に取り組むとのこと。 省内横断]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Animate Your Git Commit History with git-story]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animate-your-git-repo-with-git-story/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/animate-your-git-repo-with-git-story/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T17:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is often useful for developers to visualize aspects of their code projects. This is especially true for version control systems like Git, where understanding the team's workflow is essential. One way to approach this in Git is to draw a graph like the one you see above. You've probably]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Stopak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How stroke-dasharray Patterns Work]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366993</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-stroke-dasharray-patterns-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T19:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say you have a line in SVG:
<svg<line x1="0" y1="30" x2="500" y2="30" stroke-color="#f8a100" /</svg
You can use the stroke-dasharray property in CSS to make dashes:
line {
  stroke-dasharray: 5;
}
That 5 value is a relative unit based …
How stroke-dasharray Patterns Work originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Infrastructure as Code by Building a Custom Machine Image in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-instructure-as-a-code-by-building-custom-machine-image-in-aws/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-instructure-as-a-code-by-building-custom-machine-image-in-aws/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! If you're wondering what infrastructure-as-code means, then you've come to the right place.  In this article I will explain the concepts behind Infrastructure-As-Code (IaC) at a high level and dive into a category of IaC known as server templating.  For the purpose of this article, we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Destiny Erhabor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[strftime() Python – Datetime Format Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strftime-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/strftime-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, you can format date objects and present them in readable form using the strftime function. In this article, I'll show you how. What is strftime() in Python? strftime() is a Python date method you can use to convert dates to strings. It doesn't just convert to strings, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable and Disable Search Highlights on Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-disbale-search-highlights-on-windows-11/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-disbale-search-highlights-on-windows-11/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 is the new operating system from Microsoft. If you've been using it from the beginning after it was just released, then you've already seen some changes. Search highlights are not new for the Windows operating systems as Windows 10 also has the same feature. And you might want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[『聖剣伝説 レジェンド オブ マナ』が発売された日。自分でマップを作る“ランドメイクシステム”が斬新だった！【今日は何の日？】]]></title>
        <id>https://famitsu.com/news/202207/15268192.html</id>
        <link href="https://famitsu.com/news/202207/15268192.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[過去のこの日、ゲーム業界に何があったのかを振り返る。1999年（平成11年）7月15日は、プレイステーションで『聖剣伝説 レジェンド オブ マナ』が発売された日。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[泉佐野、天王寺…屋台のラーメンが食べたくて追いかけた]]></title>
        <id>https://dailyportalz.jp/kiji/yatai-ramen-Izumisano-Tennoji</id>
        <link href="https://dailyportalz.jp/kiji/yatai-ramen-Izumisano-Tennoji"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[屋台のラーメンが久々に食べたくて、「たまにあの辺りに来るらしい」というような噂を頼りに、がんばって追いかけてみた。 (スズキナオ)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resolving Conflicts Between Designers And Engineers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/resolving-conflicts-designers-engineers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/resolving-conflicts-designers-engineers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Scott Himmer will go over some areas where you might find the design and engineering conflicts manifesting, what some of the contributing factors are, and strategies to work through the challenges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Scott Himmer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[中2、小4の子を残し「39歳の若さで逝った夫」　意識をなくす前に妻に伝えた「予想外の言葉」（デイリー新潮）]]></title>
        <id>https://news.yahoo.co.jp/articles/822f39828b756e7262450c27bf06f20c3cf623b0</id>
        <link href="https://news.yahoo.co.jp/articles/822f39828b756e7262450c27bf06f20c3cf623b0"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T23:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[「これまでの私の人生を振り返ってみると、大きな三つの辛い出来事がありました」――そう語るのは、岸田ひろ実さん。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp.org Press Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-press-kit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-press-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T22:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the press kit for freeCodeCamp.org. Contact information: 100% of freeCodeCamp's revenue goes toward programs.  For interview requests, speaking engagements, or social media questions, please contact our founder, Quincy Larson, at quincy@freecodecamp.org. About freeCodeCamp.org Quincy Larson founded freeCodeCamp.org in 2014 to help people transition into tech careers using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Python Script – How to Execute Python Shell Commands in the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-python-script-how-to-execute-python-shell-commands-in-terminal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-python-script-how-to-execute-python-shell-commands-in-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're starting out learning a new programming language, your very first program is likely to be one that prints "hello world!".  Let's say you want to do this in Python. There are two ways of doing it: using the Python shell or writing it as a script and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Office Spaces]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366905</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/office-spaces/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it’s super timely that Jim Nielson wrote about his office space the other day. My family recently re-rooted in Colorado and I was up late last night setting up my desk and everything around it. So late, in …
Office Spaces originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use React and APIs to Build a Weather App]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-and-apis-to-build-a-weather-app/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-react-and-apis-to-build-a-weather-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A weather application is a very common beginner's programming project. But you can take this basic project to the next level by incorporating multiple APIs and autocomplete of places. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your React skills by guiding you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[フリーランスやリモートワークで働く時の生産性の高め方 : ライフハッカー［日本版］]]></title>
        <id>https://lifehacker.jp/article/how-to-schedule-your-day-when-you-freelance-or-work-from-home</id>
        <link href="https://lifehacker.jp/article/how-to-schedule-your-day-when-you-freelance-or-work-from-home"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2012年からフリーランスのライター、編集者、教師として働く著者が模索する仕事の作業効率を高める方法を紹介。午前中と早めの午後が最も仕事が捗る、午後3時を回ると、創造的な仕事ではなく受動的な作業をしたくなるなど、自分の特性を活かした働き方を伝えます。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[なぜ人間は道ばたに生えている雑草や葉っぱのほとんどを食べることができないのか？]]></title>
        <id>https://gigazine.net/news/20220714-why-cant-eat-leaf</id>
        <link href="https://gigazine.net/news/20220714-why-cant-eat-leaf"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ほうれん草やレタスなど、食材として売られている植物の「葉っぱ」は普通に食べられるものの、道端に生えている草や木の葉っぱを採って食べる人はほとんどいません。なぜ道端に生えている草は食べられないのかについて、海外メディアのUrboが植物学者のアシュリー・グレン氏に尋ねています。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[レバレジーズの未来をつくる。業務創造・改革コンテストを開催！]]></title>
        <id>https://melev.leverages.jp/entry/2022/07/12/121010</id>
        <link href="https://melev.leverages.jp/entry/2022/07/12/121010"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022年春、レバレジーズで初の試みとなる「新規事業コンテスト」がおこなわれました。このコンテストは、机上の空論ではなく、参加者全員が本気で事業化を目指して取り組むガチ企画。そんな事業会社としてのこだわりがつまった社内コンテストをレポートします。（ライター：飯野） 新規事業コンテスト「LEGO」とは？ 概要 この企画は、社員を対象とした事業創造・事業改革コンテストです。1組5人の9チーム対抗戦でおこなわれ、岩槻代表へのプレゼンで最優秀チームと採択案が決定します。 チームのリーダーを務めるのは、レバレジーズの顔ともいえる各事業の部長陣7人と一般公募から選ばれた社員2人のあわせて9人。リーダー自ら…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[圧倒的成果は、誰かの「夢中」から生まれる。ノーコードさんの正しい週末]]></title>
        <id>https://ferret-plus.com/68570</id>
        <link href="https://ferret-plus.com/68570"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[エンジニアやデザイナーの工数を気遣いながら作業を依頼する必要ないので、小さな仮説でも自由自在に即検証できるノーコード。自由度が上がることは、仕事の裁量が増えるということ。そうすると自然に仕事は楽しくなるので、思考量が増えて成果もついてくる。圧倒的成果とは、こうした誰かの「夢中」から生まれるもの。誰かの「夢中」を止めず、すぐに形にできる。そして形になることでさらに「夢中」になる。この「正」の循環を生み出してくれるのが、ノーコードのCMSツールの一番の魅力です。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[アーキテクトに求められるマインドとは / mindset for an architect]]></title>
        <id>https://speakerdeck.com/iselegant/mindset-for-an-architect</id>
        <link href="https://speakerdeck.com/iselegant/mindset-for-an-architect"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[任天堂がダイナモピクチャーズを子会社化―商号を「ニンテンドーピクチャーズ」とし、映像コンテンツ強化へ]]></title>
        <id>https://inside-games.jp/article/2022/07/14/139234.html</id>
        <link href="https://inside-games.jp/article/2022/07/14/139234.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[映像コンテンツの企画・制作会社ダイナモピクチャーズを子会社化。目的は任天堂グループの映像コンテンツの企画・制作体制を強化するためとのこと。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holograms, light-leaks and how to build CSS-only shaders.]]></title>
        <id>https://robbowen.digital/wrote-about/css-blend-mode-shaders</id>
        <link href="https://robbowen.digital/wrote-about/css-blend-mode-shaders"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a shiny WebGL look without actually using WebGL. In this article we take a look at how CSS blend modes unleash the potential of cool compositing effects without the need for JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Software Framework?]]></title>
        <id>https://freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-software-framework</id>
        <link href="https://freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-software-framework"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, companies both big and small use some kind of software framework to build their websites. And if you want to get into coding, it's important to learn and understand some of the popular frameworks – regardless of the field you choose in the industry. ‌‌‌‌But why? ‌‌‌‌ Frameworks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Nothing But Docker For Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/using-nothing-but-docker-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/using-nothing-but-docker-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using only Docker to build and run applications and commands removes the need for previous knowledge in some tool or programming language. Also, it avoids the necessity to install new modules and dependencies directly to the system, which makes development machine-independent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Raphael Amoedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use RegEx to Match Emoji – Including Discord Emotes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-regex-to-match-emoji-including-discord-emotes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-regex-to-match-emoji-including-discord-emotes/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T23:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emoji are special Unicode characters that render pictographs. But these characters can be very tricky to identify with RegEx.  I was recently working on a Discord bot that had to detect the number of emotes in a given message. Today I'll share my process with you, including the newer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Abstraction in Programming – And Why is it Useful?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-abstraction-in-programming/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-abstraction-in-programming/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T22:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that abstraction is one of the most important concepts for any software engineer to know? That's right! Without the use of abstraction when developing new technologies and concepts, we would never have been able to invent most software or even most things. So, understanding this concept is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Get Current Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-current-time/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-get-current-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T22:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your websites and applications, you might want to add functionalities like timestamps or checking the time of a user’s activity. Every programming language has modules or methods for working with time, and Python is not an exception. With the datetime and time modules of Python, you can get the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Alarms in Flutter Using the Alarm Manager Plus Package]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-alarmmanager-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/flutter-alarmmanager-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T20:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are an Android developer, when you want to schedule your application to run at a specific time in the future, you use the AlarmManager.  But if you are an iOS developer, this type of component does not exist there. So if you are a Flutter developer, what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Ben Rachel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Software Framework?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-software-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-software-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T19:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, companies both big and small use some kind of software framework to build their websites. And if you want to get into coding, it's important to learn and understand some of the popular frameworks – regardless of the field you choose in the industry. ‌‌‌‌But why? ‌‌‌‌ Frameworks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Local Branch in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-local-git-branch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-local-git-branch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T16:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're making changes to a Git repository, it's a best practice to push to a different branch first. This lets you compare changes before submitting a pull request and finally merging it. This is especially crucial when working with other developers. Your repository's main branch, which is regarded as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List.append() – How to Append to a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-append-how-to-append-to-a-list-in-python/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-append-how-to-append-to-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T15:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you append (or add) new values to an already created list in Python? I will show you how in this article. But first things first... What is a List in Python? A List is a data type that allows you to store multiple values of either the same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Multiple Repositories to Subfolders Under One Website with Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-multiple-repos-to-subfolders-under-one-website-netlify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-multiple-repos-to-subfolders-under-one-website-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T14:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there! 👋 You're probably here because you are trying to deal with hosting two separate websites or repositories under one website using Netlify. And maybe you've checked out the answers on the Netlify community page, but you are still confused. The same confusion and headache led me to write]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdulmalik Salawu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Interview Prep for Big Tech (FAANG) – And How I Became A Google Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-interview-prep-for-big-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-interview-prep-for-big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T14:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I optimized my preparation for Big Tech Interviews based on my circumstances and background.  It did not require advanced Computer Science Degrees or thousands of leetcode-style questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubin Pratap</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Hooks: The Deep Cuts]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366770</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/react-hooks-the-deep-cuts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-13T13:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hooks are reusable functions. They allow you to use state and other features (e.g. lifecycle methods and so on) without writing a class. Hook functions let us “hook into” the React state lifecycle using functional components, allowing us to manipulate …
React Hooks: The Deep Cuts originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blessing Ene Anyebe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Use Flutter for Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-should-use-flutter/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-should-use-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T20:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter is a UI toolkit and SDK which you can use to build applications. Flutter is open source and you can use it to build highly performant mobile and desktop apps.  In this article, I'll explain in detail the various benefits of using Flutter so you can decide whether]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Obumuneme Nwabude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with Python – How to Scrape Data from Twitter using Tweepy and Snscrape]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-web-scraping-tutorial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-web-scraping-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a data enthusiast, you'll likely agree that one of the richest sources of real-world data is social media. Sites like Twitter are full of data. You can use the data you can get from social media in a number of ways, like sentiment analysis (analyzing people's thoughts)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim Abayomi Ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List indexOf for Python? How to Get the Index of an Item in a List with .index()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-indexof-for-python-how-to-get-the-index-of-an-item-in-a-list-with-index/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-indexof-for-python-how-to-get-the-index-of-an-item-in-a-list-with-index/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are various techniques that we can use to get the index of a list item in Python, such as the enumerate() function, a for loop, and the index() method.  In this article, we'll focus on how to get the index of an item in a list using the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Open in Python – With Statement Syntax Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/with-open-in-python-with-statement-syntax-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/with-open-in-python-with-statement-syntax-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python programming language has various functions and statements for working with a file. The with statement and open() function are two of those statements and functions. In this article, you will learn how to use both the with statement and open()  function to work with files in Python.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise of Shadows]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366896</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/in-praise-of-shadows/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our dear friend Robin has a new essay called In Praise of Shadows. Now, before you hop over there looking for nuggets on CSS box shadows, text shadows, and shadow filters… this is not that. It’s an essay …
In Praise of Shadows originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Population vs Sample – Statistics Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/population-vs-sample-statistics-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/population-vs-sample-statistics-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T17:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with data sets and conducting a statistical analysis, you need to ensure that the data set you are using is relevant, valid, and correct. The appropriate data will help you make sure that you have a correct outcome and come to an effective conclusion and solution that solves]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git and GitHub – Version Control Basics for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-the-basics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-the-basics/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T16:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Version Control System is a tool you use to track, make, and manage changes to your software code. It's also called source control. A version control system helps developers store every change they make to a file at different stages so they and their teammates can retrieve those changes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 49 With Paul Boag: How Do You Ship A Billion-Dollar Idea?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/smashing-podcast-episode-49/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/smashing-podcast-episode-49/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we ask what qualities are required to introduce change in large organizations, how to convince management to do the right thing, and how to ship a billion-dollar idea. Vitaly talks to expert Paul Boag to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Schedule a Job in PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-schedule-a-job-in-postgresql/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-schedule-a-job-in-postgresql/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T14:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduling allows you to automate things so you don't have to do them in real time. In this article we will see how to schedule a job in PostgreSQL. We'll use pgAgent, a job scheduling agent for PostgreSQL. How to Install PostgreSQL and Stack Builder You can install pgAgent with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jagruti Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【ごめん… 】タイで『カブトガニの丸焼き』を注文してみたら中身が衝撃的すぎた]]></title>
        <id>https://rocketnews24.com/2022/07/12/1655867</id>
        <link href="https://rocketnews24.com/2022/07/12/1655867"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T13:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[バンコクからプロペラ機に乗り、そこから船に乗り、さらにはバスを乗り継いで、やってきたのは『チャーン島』なるタイ南部のノドカな離島。ノドカな気分に浸りたくてここ …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kendo UI For Angular Data Grid And Angular Material: Have Your Cake And Eat It Too]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/kendo-ui-angular-data-grid-material/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/kendo-ui-angular-data-grid-material/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-12T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Zara Cooper will examine some of the features of the Kendo UI for Angular Data Grid in comparison to those offered by the Angular Material Table.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Automated Pull Request Checklist in GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-pr-checklist-in-github/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-pr-checklist-in-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T23:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever contributed to a project, whether it's your app at work or an open-source tool, you've likely created a pull request. This requests that your code changes to merged into the main codebase. We use pull requests to ensure only quality code is merged into our main branches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brittany Joiner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Node.js – Beginner's Guide to Node]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intoduction-to-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intoduction-to-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T21:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is a JavaScript runtime that extends its capability to the server-side. It is built on Chrome’s V8 JavaScript Engine.  Node is an event-driven, non-blocking IO model. This means it's asynchronous, and doesn't block itself for one request (but rather immediately moves to the next request). This makes Node]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arash Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String Format – Formatting Strings in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-format-how-to-format-strings-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-format-how-to-format-strings-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T18:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has many string methods you can use to format strings. In this article, I'll show you some of the most commonly used methods. How to Use the toLowerCase() String Method As the name implies, you use the toLowerCase() string method to convert strings to their lowercase version. This method]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Check if Undefined – How to Test for Undefined in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-check-if-undefined-how-to-test-for-undefined-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-check-if-undefined-how-to-test-for-undefined-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T17:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An undefined variable or anything without a value will always return "undefined" in JavaScript. This is not the same as null, despite the fact that both imply an empty state.  You'll typically assign a value to a variable after you declare it, but this is not always the case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Asked TypeScript Questions on StackOverflow – Answered for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-top-stack-overflowed-typescript-questions-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-top-stack-overflowed-typescript-questions-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T15:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I hate stack overflow" — said no developer ever. While it’s helpful to have your answers a Google search away, what’s even more powerful is truly understanding the solutions you stumble upon. In this article, I’ll explore the seven most stackoverflowed TypeScript questions. I spent hours researching these. I hope]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel Ohans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenStack Tutorial – Operate Your Own Private Cloud (Full Course)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/openstack-tutorial-operate-your-own-private-cloud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/openstack-tutorial-operate-your-own-private-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T14:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenStack is an open source software that provides cloud infrastructure for virtual machines, bare metal, and containers. In this article, you will learn how to use OpenStack to operate your own private cloud. By the end of the tutorial, you will have a core understanding of what OpenStack is and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Writing for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366609</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/technical-writing-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T12:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, PHP, C++, Dart — there are so many programming languages out there and you may even be totally fluent in several of them! But as we aim to write more and better code, the way we …
Technical Writing for Developers originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eluda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look At Remix And The Differences With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/look-remix-differences-next/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/look-remix-differences-next/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about Remix, the framework to create JavaScript projects using server-side rendering. Let’s go through its main features and concepts and see the similarities and differences with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[次世代ゲーム「SEED」の開発企業が約56億円の資金調達を発表]]></title>
        <id>https://coinchoice.net/next-generation-game-seed-developer-raised-5billion</id>
        <link href="https://coinchoice.net/next-generation-game-seed-developer-raised-5billion"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T10:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ベルリンを拠点に次世代ゲーム「SEED」を開発するクラング・ゲームズ（Klang Games）が4,100万ドル（約56億円）の資金調達を行ったことを発表した。調達した資金の用途など合わせて紹介します。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[シミュレーション仮説2022：もちろん、わたしたちはシミュレーションの中で生きている]]></title>
        <id>https://wired.jp/membership/2022/07/09/living-in-a-simulation</id>
        <link href="https://wired.jp/membership/2022/07/09/living-in-a-simulation"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T10:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[生命、宇宙、そしてすべてのものが存在する理由として意味をなすのは、わたしたちがスーパーコンピューターの中に生きているという解釈だけであり、これに真っ向から反対するのは科学者たちだけだろう。さぁ、もっと自らを解き放ち、わたしたちと一緒にシミュレーション仮説を楽しもう。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[安倍元首相、街頭演説中に銃で撃たれる。岸田首相｢卑劣な蛮行、決して許せない｣【UPDATE】]]></title>
        <id>https://businessinsider.jp/post-256394</id>
        <link href="https://businessinsider.jp/post-256394"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T17:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[奈良市内で参院選候補者の応援演説中に銃撃された自民党の安倍晋三元首相が、7月8日午後5時3分に死去した。搬送先の奈良県立医科大学附属病院が会見で発表した。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Five-Step Approach To The Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/five-step-approach-metaverse/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/five-step-approach-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a designer, you may be tasked with figuring out how your company should approach the metaverse or thinking about designing for the metaverse. In this article, Lyndon Cerejo will discuss a few steps he recommends before diving headfirst into any design for the metaverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[煌めきが象徴する、アルマーニ プリヴェの現代女性像。【2022年AWクチュール速報】]]></title>
        <id>https://vogue.co.jp/fashion/article/us-vogue-2022-aw-haute-couture-armani-prive</id>
        <link href="https://vogue.co.jp/fashion/article/us-vogue-2022-aw-haute-couture-armani-prive"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T23:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[アルマーニ プリヴェ（ARMANI PRIVÉ）は今季、「プティラン（煌めき）」をテーマに掲げたコレクションを発表。無数のスパークルを放つドレスやスーツ、ニットなど、あらゆるオケージョンにフィットするアイテムが展開された。現代社会を生き抜く、あらゆる女性にフィットするモダンドレスアップを打ち出した。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[サービス別、自分がオンラインなことを相手に知られないようにする方法]]></title>
        <id>https://gizmodo.jp/2022/07/how-to-hide-online-status.html</id>
        <link href="https://gizmodo.jp/2022/07/how-to-hide-online-status.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T23:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[オンラインで作業しているんだけど、それを他の人に知られたくないときってあります。話しかけられたくない！ 無視してるって思われたくない！ いつオンになっているかで生活予測されたくない！ コイツずっとオンだなとも思われたくない！ その気持ちわかります。なので、まとめてみました。サービス別のオンライン非表示方法。ただ、その代わりと言ってはなんですが、相手がオンラインかどうか、メッセを読んだかどうかもわからなくなる仕様のものもありますので、そこはご留意ください。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[keyerror in Python – How to Fix Dictionary Error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keyerror-in-python-how-to-fix-dictionary-error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keyerror-in-python-how-to-fix-dictionary-error/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T19:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with dictionaries in Python, a KeyError gets raised when you try to access an item that doesn't exist in a Python dictionary. Here's a Python dictionary called student: student = {   "name": "John",   "course": "Python", } In the dictionary above, you can access the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reversing a String in JavaScript – Invert a string with the JS .reverse() Method]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reversing-a-string-in-javascript-invert-a-string-with-the-js-reverse-method/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reversing-a-string-in-javascript-invert-a-string-with-the-js-reverse-method/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T17:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reversing strings in JavaScript is something you'll need to do often on your web development journey. You might need to reverse a string during interviews, when solving algorithms, or when doing data manipulation. We will learn how to reverse a string in JavaScript using built-in JavaScript methods as well as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The PHP Handbook – Learn PHP for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-php-handbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-php-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T16:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PHP is an incredibly popular programming language. Statistics say it’s used by 80% of all websites. It’s the language that powers WordPress, the widely used content management system for websites. And it also powers a lot of different frameworks that make Web Development easier, like Laravel. Speaking of Laravel, it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flavio Copes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Connection is Not Private Error – How to Fix in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/your-connection-is-not-private-error-how-to-fix-in-chrome/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/your-connection-is-not-private-error-how-to-fix-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T16:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you log on to a website and your browser shows the “Your connection is not private” error, the browser is trying to warn you to stay off the website. In that case, the browser has run a check on the SSL (secure socket layer) certificate and found a problem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript DOM Manipulation Course]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-dom-manipulation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-dom-manipulation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T13:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In website development, DOM stands for Document Object Model. It is a programming interface that allows us to create, change, or remove elements from a website document. DOM manipulation is when you use JavaScript to add, remove, and modify elements of a website. It is very common in web development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Accessibility-First Approach To Chart Visual Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/accessibility-first-approach-chart-visual-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/accessibility-first-approach-chart-visual-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore how an accessibility-first approach can lead you down the path of creating a better visual design for charts. Throughout the article, you’ll learn to use the Web Content Accessibility Standards and how this approach leadd to an unexpected yet better outcome for everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kent Eisenhuth &amp; Kai Chang)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Nullable – How to Check for Null in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-nullable-how-to-check-for-null-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-nullable-how-to-check-for-null-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-07T00:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you've gotta check to make sure that nothing isn't actually...nothing. 😲❗❓  In JavaScript, null is a primitive type intentionally containing the value of null. Undefined is a primitive type and represents a variable you declare without initiating a value. So, null is nothing and undefined is just missing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eamonn Cottrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ゲッターズ飯田が見抜いた、「幸運を引き寄せる人」が意識している3つのポイント]]></title>
        <id>https://gendai.ismedia.jp/articles/-/97118</id>
        <link href="https://gendai.ismedia.jp/articles/-/97118"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T22:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[芸能界で一番有名な占い師であるゲッターズ飯田さん。この度、彼の「原点」とも言えるエッセイ集が発売された。読むと元気になり、運気がもらえる書籍『ゲッターズ飯田の占いよりも大切な話 ただそう思っただけ』から、ゲッターズ飯田さんが感じた「幸運を引き寄せる人」について、一部編集のうえ紹介しよう。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ゲッターズ飯田の五星三心（ごせいさんしん）占い 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://asahi-getters.com/2023</id>
        <link href="https://asahi-getters.com/2023"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T22:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[６万人以上を占ってきた最強占い師による「開運の書」 2023年、最新版！]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Key from a Dictionary While Iterating Over it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-key-from-the-dictionary-while-iterating-over-it-definitive-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-key-from-the-dictionary-while-iterating-over-it-definitive-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T21:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python dictionaries allow you to store values in a Key and Value format. You can access the values using the key. You can also iterate through the complete dictionary to access every element. Sometimes while iterating through the dictionary, you may need to remove a key from the dictionary. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aruchamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a List in Python – Declare Lists in Python Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-list-in-python-declare-lists-in-python-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-a-list-in-python-declare-lists-in-python-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T21:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use some of the inbuilt data structures in Python to organize and store a collection of variables.  Some of these data structures include Lists, Sets, Tuples, and Dictionaries. Each of them have their own syntax and features.  In this article, we'll focus on Lists. You'll see]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Product Designer – 2022 Product Design Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/product-designer-roadmap/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/product-designer-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T20:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Design industry is rapidly evolving, and there are many career choices in the space. You've got UI/UX Design, Product Design, Interaction Design, Motion Design, and more.  In this article, I will discuss a roadmap that will show you how to become a self-taught Digital Product Designer without a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ujah Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up GitHub User Authentication using Firebase and React (with Hooks)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-user-authentication-using-firebase-and-reactjs-with-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/github-user-authentication-using-firebase-and-reactjs-with-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T18:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I will walk you through the process of creating a GitHub User Authentication System using Firebase and React (with hooks). If you have ever tried building an authentication system before, you might agree that it can be painful. This is where Firebase steps in. Firebase provides user]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishi Purwar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An SSL Error Has Occurred – How to Fix Certificate Verification Error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-ssl-error-has-occurred-how-to-fix-certificate-verification-error/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-ssl-error-has-occurred-how-to-fix-certificate-verification-error/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re surfing the net and an SSL error occurs on a website you're trying to visit, your browser will warn you by showing you an error messages or signal. This error is mostly caused by an expired or bad SSL certificate. It also occurs when the browser can’t verify]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn JavaScript Faster – Tips and Resources to Get Started Coding JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-javascript-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-javascript-faster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T17:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a programming language commonly used for web development, among many other things. It works in conjunction with HTML and CSS to add dynamic functionality to websites. About 97% of the websites in the world use JavaScript – so you can see that it's a popular and widely-used language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annoh Karlgusta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Tutorial –  Code Two Word Games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-tutorial-code-two-word-games/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-tutorial-code-two-word-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding games is a fun way to improve your JavaScript skills. We just published a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to code two word games in JavaScript. Ania Kubów developed this course. Ania works for freeCodeCamp and has a popular tutorial YouTube channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[プレーする価値のあるWeb3ゲームはあるか？]]></title>
        <id>https://coindeskjapan.com/153908</id>
        <link href="https://coindeskjapan.com/153908"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T14:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ゲーム企業のPoliumは7月3日、Web3ゲームのための家庭用ゲーム機「Polium One」を発表した。だがこの試みには多くの問題点がある。「ニンテンドーゲ ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Pricing Page]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/designing-better-pricing-page/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/designing-better-pricing-page/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this [series of articles](/category/design-patterns/), we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 7h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update NPM Dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-update-npm-dependencies/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-update-npm-dependencies/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Node Package Manager (npm) provides various features to help you install and maintain your project's dependencies. Dependencies can become outdated over time due to bug fixes, new features, and other updates. The more project dependencies you have, the harder it is to keep up with these updates.  Outdated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Check Empty String – Checking Null or Empty in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-check-empty-string-checking-null-or-empty-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-check-empty-string-checking-null-or-empty-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a number of reasons why you might need to check if a string is empty or not. One of the most important reasons is when you're retrieving data from a database, API, or input field. In this article, you will learn how to check if a sting is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Detect Outliers in Machine Learning – 4 Methods for Outlier Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-detect-outliers-in-machine-learning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-detect-outliers-in-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T22:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever trained a machine learning model on a real-world dataset? If yes, you’ll have likely come across outliers.  Outliers are those data points that are significantly different from the rest of the dataset. They are often abnormal observations that skew the data distribution, and arise due to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GitHub Copilot with Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-github-copilot-with-visual-studio-code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-github-copilot-with-visual-studio-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T15:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, welcome! In this article, we will learn how to use the GitHub Copilot AI tool with Visual Studio Code. What is GitHub Copilot? GitHub Copilot is a tool that can help you write easier and faster code. It is powered by GPT-3. You just have to write the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishant Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Secure Source Code for Proprietary Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-secure-source-code-for-proprietary-software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-secure-source-code-for-proprietary-software/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As software developers working on proprietary software, it's our job to create programs that provide the functionality our clients need. And it's also our job to create those programs in a way that makes them easy to use, maintain, and upgrade.  But proprietary software developers have another, much more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes VS Docker Swarm – What is the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-vs-docker-swarm-what-is-the-difference/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-vs-docker-swarm-what-is-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T14:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern businesses are relying on containerization technologies to simplify the process of deploying and managing complex applications.  Containers assemble the necessary dependencies within one package. In this way, you don't need to worry about dependency-related conflicts that may arise in the production environment. Containers are portable and scalable, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Full-Stack Authentication App With React, Express, MongoDB, Heroku, and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-fullstack-authentication-system-with-react-express-mongodb-heroku-and-netlify/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-fullstack-authentication-system-with-react-express-mongodb-heroku-and-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T13:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's almost impossible to build an application without registration and login functionalities. But this can be a bit tricky for beginners. In this article, I will guide you through creating a full-stack authentication application. You will start with the backend which will be built with Express and hosted on Heroku]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Njoku Samson Ebere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Localized Website With Hugo And Strapi]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/build-localized-website-hugo-strapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/build-localized-website-hugo-strapi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-05T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, Zara Cooper explains how to use Strapi’s Internationalization feature to create content in multiple languages. You’ll also learn how to create a Hugo site that consumes localized content from Strapi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating UX Maturity With A Breakthrough Project]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/accelerating-ux-maturity-breakthrough-project/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/07/accelerating-ux-maturity-breakthrough-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-04T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, John Scott Bowie shares the story of 40 years of attempts to advance corporate UX maturity that — after numerous initiatives with marginal results — culminated in a breakthrough project that accelerated a company’s UX maturity from “Emergent” to “User-Driven” in less than a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (John Scott Bowie)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[auの障害、報告ページを見るだけで胃が痛い…一時間に一回、進展のない事を淡々と報告せざるを得ないリリース「ある意味これは誠意」]]></title>
        <id>https://togetter.com/li/1910450</id>
        <link href="https://togetter.com/li/1910450"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T09:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[現場のみなさま、本当にお疲れ様です]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[アメリカで銀行口座を持たない若者が急増中。web3時代、世界の“お金観”はこう変わる]]></title>
        <id>https://r25.jp/article/1090813431828391221</id>
        <link href="https://r25.jp/article/1090813431828391221"/>
        <updated>2022-07-03T00:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[伊藤穰一著『テクノロジーが予測する未来 web3、メタバース、NFTで世界はこうなる』より]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[英語でゲーム] The Elder Scrolls Online]]></title>
        <id>https://anti-social-diary.blogspot.com/2019/02/elder-scrolls-online.html</id>
        <link href="https://anti-social-diary.blogspot.com/2019/02/elder-scrolls-online.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T09:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls Online は、その名の通り、The Elder Scrollsシリーズのオンラインゲーム。     英語音声あり、英語字幕あり。DMMで買うと英語でプレイできないと思われるので、ZOS(Zenimax Online Studio)の公式サ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[地方移住って実際どうなの？メルペイ・ミラティブで働くエンジニアに聞いたメリット・デメリット]]></title>
        <id>https://engineer-lab.findy-code.io/event_local</id>
        <link href="https://engineer-lab.findy-code.io/event_local"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T02:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[コロナ禍で地方移住を検討するエンジニアが増えている中、ファインディでは「ぶっちゃけ地方移住ってどうなの？実際移住したエンジニアにメリデメを聞いてみる」と題したイベントを開催。東京から地方に移住した上田さんと近藤さんにお話をお伺いしました。 移住して感じたことについて質問してみると、お二人ともが「移住してよかった」と回答。一方で「子どもの教育面」「コロナ禍でのコミュニティのあり方」については、考える必要があるともお話してくださいました。 本稿では、イベント中に語られた地方移住の実情についてまとめています。 パネリスト 上田拓也さん / @tenntenn 株式会社メルペイ バックエンドエンジニア…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[海外でB2B企業ブランディングが重要な理由と優れた事例6選 デザイン会社 ビートラックス : ブログ]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.btrax.com/jp/b2b-branding</id>
        <link href="https://blog.btrax.com/jp/b2b-branding"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T00:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[「B2B企業にブランディングは必要ですか？」これはよく聞かれる質問ですが、グローバル展開を目指すのであればブランディングは必須と言えます。今回はアメリカのB2B企業による秀逸なブランディングキャンペーンをご紹介。B2B企業ながら一般消費者の記憶にも残るような、エンターテインメント性の高さにご注目ください。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[個人の音声データを“匿名化”せよ：認識技術の普及で高まるプライバシー保護の重要性]]></title>
        <id>https://wired.jp/article/voice-recognition-privacy-speech-changer</id>
        <link href="https://wired.jp/article/voice-recognition-privacy-speech-changer"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T00:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[音声アシスタントや音声認識技術が普及するにつれ、「人間の声」から読み取れる情報の価値が高まっている。個人の特定のみならず感情や健康状態の読み取りまで可能になるなか、ターゲット広告への利用や“なりすまし”に対抗すべく、データの匿名化によりプライバシーを守る機運が高まり始めた。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[裏バイト:逃亡禁止]]></title>
        <id>https://urasunday.com/title/1155/187864</id>
        <link href="https://urasunday.com/title/1155/187864"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T00:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[命に値札を付けろ。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Import SVGs in a React and Vite app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-import-svgs-in-react-and-vite/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-import-svgs-in-react-and-vite/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T22:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you having difficulties importing SVGs into your React app? This is a problem that many developers face, especially when setting up a new React app with a module bundler. In this article, I will share with you the different ways of importing SVGs in React, as well as how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Mitolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String Comparison – How to Compare Strings in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-comparison-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-comparison-how-to-compare-strings-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T22:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may want to compare two strings to know which is higher or lower alphabetically or to see if they are equal. You can do this in many ways. I'll show you two of them in this article. 1. How to Compare Strings Using localeCompare You can use the localeCompare]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Else-If Statement Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-else-if-statement-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-else-if-statement-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T22:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conditional statements are helpful for decision-making and are a core concept in all programming languages. In this article, you will learn how to write conditional statements in Python. Specifically, you will learn how to write if, if else, and elif (also known as  else if) statements in Python. Here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collective Nouns for the Web]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366689</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/collective-nouns-for-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melanie Sumner has this super-specific collection of web-related nouns for describing a group or set of something. You know how there’s a school or fish or a herd of cows? Same sort of thing, but for funny web jargon.
Things …
Collective Nouns for the Web originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Track Machine Learning Experiments with HarperDB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/track-machine-learning-experiments-with-harperdb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/track-machine-learning-experiments-with-harperdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T17:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Properly tracking your machine learning experiments is easier than you think. When working on a machine learning project, you will conduct different machine learning experiments before you reach the final ML model with the best performance.  Here are some possible machine learning experiments you might conduct:  * Testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davis David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use VLOOKUP in Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-vlookup-in-excel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-vlookup-in-excel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T16:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working in Excel, the VLOOKUP function makes looking up information less time-consuming. This is particularly true when you're using more than one Excel sheet. In this article, you will learn what the VLOOKUP function does, as well as understand the syntax behind it. You will also learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battery Icon Not Showing – How to Restore Missing Battery Icon in Windows PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/battery-icon-not-showing-how-to-restore-missing-battery-icon-in-windows-pc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/battery-icon-not-showing-how-to-restore-missing-battery-icon-in-windows-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T15:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’re working with your Windows PC and you discover you can’t find the battery icon in the taskbar. You even expand hidden icons and you still can’t find the battery icon. This could result in a negative effect on your productivity – because if you don't plug your laptop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[世界初「絵柄を何度でも変えられるタトゥー」が登場！セレブ御用達アーティスト開発のMagic Inkとは]]></title>
        <id>https://front-row.jp/_ct/17552366</id>
        <link href="https://front-row.jp/_ct/17552366"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T14:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[セレブ御用達のタトゥーアーティスト、バンバン（Bang Bang）が、描き替えられるタトゥーを発表した。（フロントロウ編集部）]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>My Reading List: Read and Unread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Single Element Loaders: Going 3D!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=366544</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/single-element-loaders-going-3d/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-01T13:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this fourth and final article of our little series on single-element loaders, we are going to explore 3D patterns. When creating a 3D element, it’s hard to imagine that just one HTML element is enough to simulate something like all six faces of a cube. But  maybe we can get away …
Single Element Loaders: Going 3D! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>